It's time to get over ourselves.
I think it's time to turn a corner.
I think for a lot of us up until this point,
you know, we've become trapped in a stupor of pain
and frustration and shock at just, I guess,
truly realizing the sickness of the world we're in.
And we have to understand that it was always that.
That was always taking place.
When you study history,
you know that that's not something that is new.
It may just be new to the region you're in
or new to the feed on your Instagram,
but it has been here and apparent.
And when you realize that, you say to yourself,
well, that means that I'm late to the party.
And so I need to catch the fuck up.
And catching the fuck up means ceasing paralysis.
You know, like you gotta start moving now.
We gotta start moving.
I know some of y'all might think like,
well, what are you talking about?
Like we've been protesting, et cetera.
But what I mean is that we cannot allow ourselves
to get stuck in the stasis of fear.
We have to now expand ourselves,
our physical, mental, and emotional capabilities
to reflect how to manage and improve the world
that we have been in the whole time.
It has only been our privilege saving us.
So it's time to get over ourselves.
It's time.
All of us who've been like...
It's time to get over ourselves.
The shit is hitting the fan.
It been hitting the fan in Palestine.
It's going to continue hitting the fan.
So it's time to turn the corner and get stronger
and get smarter and get more resourceful
and let that impact your hope,
let that impact your vision
and let that impact your resilience.
Yeah, it's time.
It's time.
So we gotta do what I've always said we gotta do,
which is we have to save ourselves.
Furthermore, we really need to get up and get in the fight.
And I know there's a lot of you who are gonna be like,
I've been in the fight and I think that is incredible
and kudos to you.
And when it comes to America
and black advocacy, I know that I have been in the fight.
But on a global scale,
which is the community that we're in,
a lot of us simply have been cut off
by just being American and that has to stop.
So we need to get up.
We need to start getting in a different way of life,
in a different mode of existence
to not only, when I say save ourselves,
I mean as humans, be a part of changing
and saving this fucking earth.
But we know that we are a part of that.
And so the selflessness in our ability to acknowledge like,
okay, how do I become a better part
of the global consciousness raising does serve you.
That's for anybody out there who was, you know,
selfish and didn't wanna admit it to yourself.
Helping others does help you.